newmediarockstars.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy - New Media Rockstars

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the NewMediaRockstars.com and NewMediaRockstars, INC. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to NewMediaRockstars, INC. include NewMediaRockstars.com and NMR. The NMR website is a Blog, News, and Entertainment site. By using the NMR website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

##### TRUSTe Privacy Program

NMR is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at [info@newrockstars.wpengine.com](mailto:info@newrockstars.wpengine.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). TRUSTe may serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

##### Collection of your Personal Information

NMR may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase NMR’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. NMR may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NMR. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NMR website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through NMR’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

NMR encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from NMR so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. NMR is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the NMR website.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

##### Use of your Personal Information

NMR collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

NMR may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from NMR and its affiliates. NMR may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

NMR does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

NMR may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. NMR may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NMR, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

NMR may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within NMR, in order to determine what NMR services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within NMR to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

NMR will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NMR or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NMR; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NMR, or the public.

##### Use of Cookies

The NMR website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NMR pages, or register with NMR site or services, a cookie helps NMR to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NMR website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NMR features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NMR services or websites you visit.

##### Security of your Personal Information

Verisign

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

Verisign is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust. Verisign provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity and intellectual property. By clicking on the Verisign logo, the Verisign website will serve up a web page that confirms that NMR is “Verisign Authenticated.”

##### Children Under Thirteen

NMR does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

##### Disconnecting your NMR Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your NMR account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR NMR ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their “My Account” page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone.

##### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from NMR by contacting us [here](http://http//newmediarockstars.com/contact/).

##### Changes to this Statement

NMR will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. NMR encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NMR is protecting your information.

#### Contact Information

NMR welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that NMR has not adhered to this Statement, please contact NMR at:

NewMediaRockstars, INC.

15635 alton pkwy # 325

Irvine, California 92618

Email Address:

Telephone number:

Effective as of December 01, 2011
